[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 14, "question": "Has he sealed the deal yet?", "question_tokens": ["Has", "he", "sealed", "the", "deal", "yet", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 15, "answer": "Well, that's an understatement, Piers, to say pretty good.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "that", "'s", "an", "understatement", ",", "Piers", ",", "to", "say", "pretty", "good", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama"]}, "docId": "120110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 21, "question": "Is that going to be the consistent strategy going forward?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "going", "to", "be", "the", "consistent", "strategy", "going", "forward", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 22, "answer": "Well, he's been consistent in focusing on Barack Obama.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "he", "'s", "been", "consistent", "in", "focusing", "on", "Barack", "Obama", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ron Paul", "Mitt Romney"]}, "docId": "120110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 31, "question": "Are you taking him seriously now as a possible threat to win the nomination?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "taking", "him", "seriously", "now", "as", "a", "possible", "threat", "to", "win", "the", "nomination", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 32, "answer": "Well, Ron Paul and Mitt Romney don't agree on many things.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "Ron", "Paul", "and", "Mitt", "Romney", "do", "n't", "agree", "on", "many", "things", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 40, "question": "How do you answer the charge that Mitt Romney is a vulture?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "answer", "the", "charge", "that", "Mitt", "Romney", "is", "a", "vulture", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 41, "answer": "Well, first of all, it's inaccurate and unfair.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "it", "'s", "inaccurate", "and", "unfair", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 50, "question": "Are you concerned that one of your opponents now has the kind of financial muscle to play dirty in the way that you have?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "concerned", "that", "one", "of", "your", "opponents", "now", "has", "the", "kind", "of", "financial", "muscle", "to", "play", "dirty", "in", "the", "way", "that", "you", "have", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 51, "answer": "Well, I don't think we say -- you're saying we had money.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "we", "say", "--", "you", "'re", "saying", "we", "had", "money", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 93, "question": "But can you move from dangerous to electable, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["But", "can", "you", "move", "from", "dangerous", "to", "electable", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "TO", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 94, "answer": "Well, we're dangerous to the status quo.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "we", "'re", "dangerous", "to", "the", "status", "quo", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBP", "CD", "NNS", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NNPS", "RB", ",", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", ",", "CD", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "DT", "``", "NN", "''", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 100, "question": "Why did he stick his neck out like that?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "did", "he", "stick", "his", "neck", "out", "like", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 101, "answer": "Well, there are two things that should bring all Republicans together, and that is, one is realizing that, you know, the media will pull some \"gotcha\" statements from time to time and take things out of context.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "there", "are", "two", "things", "that", "should", "bring", "all", "Republicans", "together", ",", "and", "that", "is", ",", "one", "is", "realizing", "that", ",", "you", "know", ",", "the", "media", "will", "pull", "some", "``", "gotcha", "''", "statements", "from", "time", "to", "time", "and", "take", "things", "out", "of", "context", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 114, "question": "It's going to get more serious, doesn't it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "going", "to", "get", "more", "serious", ",", "does", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJR", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 115, "answer": "It is.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 123, "question": "And finally and quickly, where does he get his energy from?", "question_tokens": ["And", "finally", "and", "quickly", ",", "where", "does", "he", "get", "his", "energy", "from", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "CC", "RB", ",", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 124, "answer": "From the people.", "answer_tokens": ["From", "the", "people", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney", "Rick Santorum", "Newt Gingrich"], "PERCENT": ["40 percent"]}, "docId": "120110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CD", ",", "CD", "NN", ",", "RB", ",", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "CC", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", ",", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 135, "question": "What do you think we've ended up at?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "we", "'ve", "ended", "up", "at", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 136, "answer": "Big victory for Mitt Romney, 39, 40 percent, very, very impressive in a crowded field like that and from his perspective, the two candidates he probably feared the most, Rick Santorum and Newt Gingrich, they did not do well coming in fourth and fifth.", "answer_tokens": ["Big", "victory", "for", "Mitt", "Romney", ",", "39", ",", "40", "percent", ",", "very", ",", "very", "impressive", "in", "a", "crowded", "field", "like", "that", "and", "from", "his", "perspective", ",", "the", "two", "candidates", "he", "probably", "feared", "the", "most", ",", "Rick", "Santorum", "and", "Newt", "Gingrich", ",", "they", "did", "not", "do", "well", "coming", "in", "fourth", "and", "fifth", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 138, "question": "John King, the big question, I guess, is of all the other runners and writers, have any of them got it in them to actually challenge Mitt Romney in South Carolina and going forward?", "question_tokens": ["John", "King", ",", "the", "big", "question", ",", "I", "guess", ",", "is", "of", "all", "the", "other", "runners", "and", "writers", ",", "have", "any", "of", "them", "got", "it", "in", "them", "to", "actually", "challenge", "Mitt", "Romney", "in", "South", "Carolina", "and", "going", "forward", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "RB", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 139, "answer": "Almost forget the candidates for a minute.", "answer_tokens": ["Almost", "forget", "the", "candidates", "for", "a", "minute", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["John King", "Mitt Romney"], "LOCATION": ["South Carolina"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 152, "question": "Well, how can you claim you're stronger if you keep losing to the candidate you call weak or freak?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "how", "can", "you", "claim", "you", "'re", "stronger", "if", "you", "keep", "losing", "to", "the", "candidate", "you", "call", "weak", "or", "freak", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 153, "answer": "Exactly.", "answer_tokens": ["Exactly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "VBN", "NN", "JJR", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", ",", "DT", "NNPS", ",", "TO", "VB", "DT", "VBN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 154, "question": "It's hard to make that argument, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "hard", "to", "make", "that", "argument", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 155, "answer": "And tell you, we had a spirited debate earlier about whether it was to the party's advantage, the Republicans, to have an extended battle.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "tell", "you", ",", "we", "had", "a", "spirited", "debate", "earlier", "about", "whether", "it", "was", "to", "the", "party", "'s", "advantage", ",", "the", "Republicans", ",", "to", "have", "an", "extended", "battle", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBP", "DT", "WP", "NN", "IN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 159, "question": "It goes on, could Romney not become a more formidable opponent?", "question_tokens": ["It", "goes", "on", ",", "could", "Romney", "not", "become", "a", "more", "formidable", "opponent", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", ",", "MD", "NNP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "RBR", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 160, "answer": "There are those who argue that, who believes that.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "are", "those", "who", "argue", "that", ",", "who", "believes", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 180, "question": "He's going to go for it, isn't he, through the super PAC?", "question_tokens": ["He", "'s", "going", "to", "go", "for", "it", ",", "is", "n't", "he", ",", "through", "the", "super", "PAC", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 181, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 202, "question": "Who's going to win this argument?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "'s", "going", "to", "win", "this", "argument", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 203, "answer": "This is going to be really difficult.", "answer_tokens": ["This", "is", "going", "to", "be", "really", "difficult", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Iowa", "South Carolina"]}, "docId": "120110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 223, "question": "Could he take some of that time and some of that voting away from Mitt Romney because they (INAUDIBLE)?", "question_tokens": ["Could", "he", "take", "some", "of", "that", "time", "and", "some", "of", "that", "voting", "away", "from", "Mitt", "Romney", "because", "they", "(", "INAUDIBLE", ")", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 224, "answer": "Here's the difference between Iowa and South Carolina.", "answer_tokens": ["Here", "'s", "the", "difference", "between", "Iowa", "and", "South", "Carolina", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 242, "question": "If Mitt Romney wins in South Carolina, is he basically the nominee?", "question_tokens": ["If", "Mitt", "Romney", "wins", "in", "South", "Carolina", ",", "is", "he", "basically", "the", "nominee", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 243, "answer": "He's not -- it isn't a done deal yet.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "'s", "not", "--", "it", "is", "n't", "a", "done", "deal", "yet", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"], "LOCATION": ["South Carolina"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "RB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 245, "question": "Erin?", "question_tokens": ["Erin", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 246, "answer": "Well, I would agree with that but I would think the momentum would be so much behind him.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "would", "agree", "with", "that", "but", "I", "would", "think", "the", "momentum", "would", "be", "so", "much", "behind", "him", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 250, "question": "David, three out of three, a done deal?", "question_tokens": ["David", ",", "three", "out", "of", "three", ",", "a", "done", "deal", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "CD", "IN", "IN", "CD", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 251, "answer": "Done deal.", "answer_tokens": ["Done", "deal", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["David"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 252, "question": "John?", "question_tokens": ["John", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 253, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New Hampshire"]}, "docId": "120110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 267, "question": "Being in the 1 percent is the last place you want to find yourself, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["Being", "in", "the", "1", "percent", "is", "the", "last", "place", "you", "want", "to", "find", "yourself", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 268, "answer": "Well, we didn't compete in New Hampshire so it doesn't surprise us that our score there was a bit on the low side.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "we", "did", "n't", "compete", "in", "New", "Hampshire", "so", "it", "does", "n't", "surprise", "us", "that", "our", "score", "there", "was", "a", "bit", "on", "the", "low", "side", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["1 percent"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["South Carolina"]}, "docId": "120110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 277, "question": "What are you going to do to turn around your fortunes given the fairly (INAUDIBLE) state you're in at the moment?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "you", "going", "to", "do", "to", "turn", "around", "your", "fortunes", "given", "the", "fairly", "(", "INAUDIBLE", ")", "state", "you", "'re", "in", "at", "the", "moment", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBN", "DT", "RB", ":", "NNP", ":", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 278, "answer": "Well, the fact is that there's a lot going to happen in the next two weeks in South Carolina.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "fact", "is", "that", "there", "'s", "a", "lot", "going", "to", "happen", "in", "the", "next", "two", "weeks", "in", "South", "Carolina", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 290, "question": "For any candidate to actually seriously challenge him for the nomination, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["For", "any", "candidate", "to", "actually", "seriously", "challenge", "him", "for", "the", "nomination", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "RB", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 291, "answer": "Well, I don't think so.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 298, "question": "Why have you found the debates such a struggle?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "have", "you", "found", "the", "debates", "such", "a", "struggle", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 299, "answer": "Well, actually, the last three or four debates I think we performed at a rather high level.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "actually", ",", "the", "last", "three", "or", "four", "debates", "I", "think", "we", "performed", "at", "a", "rather", "high", "level", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 312, "question": "Because if Mitt Romney now wins the nomination, haven't you just landed Barack Obama a perfect stick to beat him with?", "question_tokens": ["Because", "if", "Mitt", "Romney", "now", "wins", "the", "nomination", ",", "have", "n't", "you", "just", "landed", "Barack", "Obama", "a", "perfect", "stick", "to", "beat", "him", "with", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 313, "answer": "Well, there's a real difference between a venture capitalist and a vulture capitalist.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "there", "'s", "a", "real", "difference", "between", "a", "venture", "capitalist", "and", "a", "vulture", "capitalist", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney", "Barack Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 321, "question": "What is the realistic endgame for you if you reach that point?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "realistic", "endgame", "for", "you", "if", "you", "reach", "that", "point", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 322, "answer": "Well, I think you said the magic words, if I meet that point, which is not in our game plan at all.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "you", "said", "the", "magic", "words", ",", "if", "I", "meet", "that", "point", ",", "which", "is", "not", "in", "our", "game", "plan", "at", "all", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 341, "question": "What's your assessment?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "your", "assessment", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 342, "answer": "Well, no doubt about it, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "no", "doubt", "about", "it", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["South Carolina"]}, "docId": "120110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 350, "question": "Or is it good for the party?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "is", "it", "good", "for", "the", "party", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 351, "answer": "Well, this is South Carolina.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "this", "is", "South", "Carolina", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "NNS", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 358, "question": "I mean is it a good thing to wrap it up early or can you see the merits of a good old tussle?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "is", "it", "a", "good", "thing", "to", "wrap", "it", "up", "early", "or", "can", "you", "see", "the", "merits", "of", "a", "good", "old", "tussle", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RP", "RB", "CC", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 359, "answer": "ONNELLY: You know, I really think, Piers, that a long, drawn-out battle is not necessarily a bad thing because it engages people nationwide.", "answer_tokens": ["ONNELLY", ":", "You", "know", ",", "I", "really", "think", ",", "Piers", ",", "that", "a", "long", ",", "drawn-out", "battle", "is", "not", "necessarily", "a", "bad", "thing", "because", "it", "engages", "people", "nationwide", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 367, "question": "Is that going to be a problem for him, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "going", "to", "be", "a", "problem", "for", "him", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 368, "answer": "Well, you know, we are fiercely evangelical.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "we", "are", "fiercely", "evangelical", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 404, "question": "Who are you endorsing right now?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "are", "you", "endorsing", "right", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 405, "answer": "Nobody.", "answer_tokens": ["Nobody", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBG", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 415, "question": "And you can dismiss him but what more can he be doing than he is doing?", "question_tokens": ["And", "you", "can", "dismiss", "him", "but", "what", "more", "can", "he", "be", "doing", "than", "he", "is", "doing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "CC", "WP", "JJR", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 416, "answer": "Well, he's playing a very good game of defense when he has a lot of money working to his benefit and he's playing defense.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "he", "'s", "playing", "a", "very", "good", "game", "of", "defense", "when", "he", "has", "a", "lot", "of", "money", "working", "to", "his", "benefit", "and", "he", "'s", "playing", "defense", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 422, "question": "Can I get behind this guy the way that I got behind John McCain?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "I", "get", "behind", "this", "guy", "the", "way", "that", "I", "got", "behind", "John", "McCain", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 423, "answer": "OK.", "answer_tokens": ["OK", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["John McCain"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 428, "question": "I mean he's not doing badly for somebody that everyone else says they're not very enthusiastic about?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "he", "'s", "not", "doing", "badly", "for", "somebody", "that", "everyone", "else", "says", "they", "'re", "not", "very", "enthusiastic", "about", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "NN", "WDT", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 429, "answer": "Well, he is winning.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "he", "is", "winning", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "VBN", "NNS", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 443, "question": "But who do you think he would have been steering to?", "question_tokens": ["But", "who", "do", "you", "think", "he", "would", "have", "been", "steering", "to", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "VBG", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 444, "answer": "Oh, my father never got involved in contested primaries for very good reasons and, in fact, would support the nominee of the party.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "my", "father", "never", "got", "involved", "in", "contested", "primaries", "for", "very", "good", "reasons", "and", ",", "in", "fact", ",", "would", "support", "the", "nominee", "of", "the", "party", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Republican Party", "Republican Party"], "PERSON": ["Barack Obama"]}, "docId": "120110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "VBP", "IN", "CC", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBN", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 457, "question": "Barack Obama's got it all to do, hasn't he?", "question_tokens": ["Barack", "Obama", "'s", "got", "it", "all", "to", "do", ",", "has", "n't", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "PRP", "DT", "TO", "VB", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 458, "answer": "Well, what's happened over the last few months is -- we've had a focus on the Republican Party and the Republican candidates with the media focusing on the Republican Party and what does it stand for and it's been a diversion from what does Barack Obama stand for and what has he been able to do.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "what", "'s", "happened", "over", "the", "last", "few", "months", "is", "--", "we", "'ve", "had", "a", "focus", "on", "the", "Republican", "Party", "and", "the", "Republican", "candidates", "with", "the", "media", "focusing", "on", "the", "Republican", "Party", "and", "what", "does", "it", "stand", "for", "and", "it", "'s", "been", "a", "diversion", "from", "what", "does", "Barack", "Obama", "stand", "for", "and", "what", "has", "he", "been", "able", "to", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers Morgan"]}, "docId": "120110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 491, "question": "So what do you think of the new politics where everyone just whacks everybody else?", "question_tokens": ["So", "what", "do", "you", "think", "of", "the", "new", "politics", "where", "everyone", "just", "whacks", "everybody", "else", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "WRB", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 492, "answer": "Well, I don't think you know me, Piers Morgan.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "you", "know", "me", ",", "Piers", "Morgan", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 511, "question": "He didn't believe Republicans should do this to each other, did he?", "question_tokens": ["He", "did", "n't", "believe", "Republicans", "should", "do", "this", "to", "each", "other", ",", "did", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "DT", "TO", "DT", "JJ", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 512, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 530, "question": "The fact that he's now turning mean, I guess, is the story because he tried to present himself as the new Newt, the nice Newt, the saintly Newt and it didn't work and now he's going to go back to the way perhaps a more traditional Newt would have behaved which is when an opponent whacks him he's going to whack him back, isn't he?", "question_tokens": ["The", "fact", "that", "he", "'s", "now", "turning", "mean", ",", "I", "guess", ",", "is", "the", "story", "because", "he", "tried", "to", "present", "himself", "as", "the", "new", "Newt", ",", "the", "nice", "Newt", ",", "the", "saintly", "Newt", "and", "it", "did", "n't", "work", "and", "now", "he", "'s", "going", "to", "go", "back", "to", "the", "way", "perhaps", "a", "more", "traditional", "Newt", "would", "have", "behaved", "which", "is", "when", "an", "opponent", "whacks", "him", "he", "'s", "going", "to", "whack", "him", "back", ",", "is", "n't", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", ",", "DT", "RB", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "RB", "DT", "RBR", "JJ", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "WDT", "VBZ", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RB", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 531, "answer": "I think it was very disingenuous.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "was", "very", "disingenuous", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Newt"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 541, "question": "Has he won?", "question_tokens": ["Has", "he", "won", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 542, "answer": "Oh, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 590, "question": "Has he still got a chance do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Has", "he", "still", "got", "a", "chance", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 591, "answer": "Not much of a chance.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "much", "of", "a", "chance", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Romney"]}, "docId": "120110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "VBG", "TO", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 599, "question": "Where's the smart money going now?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "'s", "the", "smart", "money", "going", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 600, "answer": "It's all going to Romney.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "all", "going", "to", "Romney", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 623, "question": "And the other question I want to put to you, if you're Barack Obama, would you rather know who the nominee is now or are you happy to watch the Republicans scrap it out for a few more months?", "question_tokens": ["And", "the", "other", "question", "I", "want", "to", "put", "to", "you", ",", "if", "you", "'re", "Barack", "Obama", ",", "would", "you", "rather", "know", "who", "the", "nominee", "is", "now", "or", "are", "you", "happy", "to", "watch", "the", "Republicans", "scrap", "it", "out", "for", "a", "few", "more", "months", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "TO", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "WP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNPS", "NN", "PRP", "RP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "RBR", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 624, "answer": "There's no question it's the latter.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "'s", "no", "question", "it", "'s", "the", "latter", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 634, "question": "Do both of you agree Mitt Romney at the moment looks like a shoo-in?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "both", "of", "you", "agree", "Mitt", "Romney", "at", "the", "moment", "looks", "like", "a", "shoo-in", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 635, "answer": "He's the favorite.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "'s", "the", "favorite", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 636, "question": "I'd say upward of 90 percent?", "question_tokens": ["I", "'d", "say", "upward", "of", "90", "percent", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "IN", "CD", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 637, "answer": "Ninety percent.", "answer_tokens": ["Ninety", "percent", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["90 percent"]}}]